Miss Tai, you need to understand,
only you know what happened to
the victim.
I only took the gas cylinder
from his backpack
I don't know anything else.
What did you give Jarvis, you bloody witch?
You killed him...
It got out of hand.
There's no turning back now.
(Three months after the incident)
The kids from Agent J knew about
Ngai Ka-yan's death and the stink bomb.
Something is not right.
They renamed the livestreaming
"Live from Sorry Sir".
They're obviously showing off
they had you surrounded.
They're a team.
The kid I was chasing was their head.
Did you notice anything else?
No. They were really fast.
I didn't see anything.
They even knew I go by Gogo Sir.
They're definitely connected to
Ngai Ka-yan's death.
(The day of the incident)
What happened? How come...
What did you give Jarvis, you bloody witch?
Oxygen.
Oxygen wouldn't have killed Jarvis!
You killed him...
Hey, stop it!
Get out of my way...
Calm down!
She killed Jarvis...
It's her...Jarvis is gone!
Listen to me...
Get away from me...it's her!
Calm down...
Hello! We're from the Crime Unit,
New Territories East.
Oh...what is it, Officer?
During the livestreaming of
the Static Apnea Challenge,
director Ngai Ka-yan died from
inhaling a dangerous gas.
We're here to gather evidence.
Jarvis is dead?!
What happened?
Calm down...what should we call you?
I'm Yuen Kit-ching. I'm the cleaning lady.
Auntie Ching, can you show us
Ngai Ka-yan's office?
It's over there, but he went out.
The door is locked, you need to
wait for him...
How did he die?
Do you have a spare key?
I think he had the only key.
Cheong, call and find out
if Ngai Ka-yan had the key on him.
Mr. Tsang Chun-kit,
according to people at the scene,
you and your partner Hung Tzi-long
were responsible for
the oxygen cylinders used in
the Static Apnea Challenge,
including the one Ngai Ka-yan
inhaled from, is that right?
Please answer the question.
Yes.
But on the bench next to the pool,
we collected 20 portable oxygen cylinders.
After testing, they do not contain oxygen,
but hydrogen sulfide (H2S),
or what we call a stink bomb.
(For Static Apnea Challenge)
Hung Tzi-long, in a unit on the 18/F
of Hing Fong Factory Building,
this is what we found.
Did you use it to make stink bombs
with Tsang Chun-kit?
Yes.
We made 20 cylinders
to pull a prank on Jarvis.
OK! You said you were making stink bombs.
But inside the cylinder Ngai Ka-yan used,
our Forensics colleagues found
over 1000 ppm of H2S.
That was a lethal dosage.
Low concentration of H2S will only
smell like rotten egg.
That's why they call it a stink bomb.
It will only cause slight discomfort.
But a high concentration is different,
it becomes colorless and odorless.
A whiff of it can knock you out
and may even be lethal.
I didn't know the concentration
was that high.
I only followed Tom's formula to make
the stink bombs.
I'm quite sure about the quantity.
It was meant to be a prank on Jarvis.
For the livestreaming of the Challenge,
Ngai Ka-yan decided to do it himself
the last minute.
Then he died suddenly.
Your colleagues told us
you had a run-in with Ngai Ka-yan
over filming
and you resented him.
In terms of motive and murder weapon,
you're the prime suspect.
We'd like to hear your explanation.
Sir, I never meant to kill Jarvis.
I know why you think I have a motive.
But everyone knew we didn't get along,
why would I brazenly kill him
in front of everyone during a livestreaming?
What happened?
We followed the formula to
make the stink bombs.
Everything checked out.
I don't know what happened.
Why is Jarvis dead?
We may not get along lately,
but I still remember how
he helped us back then.
(Two years ago)
Peter Piper picked a peck of
pickled peppers.
She sells seashells by the seashore.
Folks, you just saw how good Hongkongers
are with tongue twisters.
If you want to watch more street games,
remember to CLS, comment, like
and share this video.
See you next time.
You're shooting for an online channel.
Speaking like a pro.
Here's your agreed pay.
But...$2,000 is hardly enough.
I have loads of other games.
If you're interested,
I can raise your pay to $20K.
This game is simple.
You see two buckets up there.
One is clear water, the other is watercolor.
I don't care how,
if you pick the bucket of water,
the $20K is yours.
But if you picked the watercolor,
sorry, kiss the money goodbye.
50/50? That's tough.
Wait, we'll pull the rope together.
One of us will get it right.
Then we can split the money.
One on each side?
Of course!
Any way we want?
Yes!
Deal!
Almost...get a close up.
Go get him...
Look...a blade of grass!
This way...a tissue!
Hey...how do you feel? Cold? Comfy?
You jerk!
Chill!
You want money, right? Here's $100K.
Have fun picking them up.
Finders keepers.
Folks, time flies and it's the end
of our livestreaming.
You think they made out like a bandit?
I'll let you in on a secret.
It's fake money.
Stay tuned to J Weekly.
Don't forget to like, comment and share.
See you next time. Bye!
It's fake money.
That's enough! You poured pigswill on us
and gave us fake money.
We need a gimmick in our video
to attract viewers. Look at them...
Here's your $20K. All yours.
This time for real.
Forget it.
We spent less than an hour. Forget it.
Jarvis, in ten minutes,
we have over 10K views
and 10K likes.
They said it's very entertaining
and those two are hilarious.
They said you're smart.
By the way, I'm Jarvis.
The creator and director of J Weekly.
We'll be filming more pranks.
You guys have quick reflexes
and are a good sport.
Would you like to join us and make money?
Shake on it and we're friends.
Don't con us with fake money again.
Your turn...
What are you doing? Get away from me!
Give me a hand. Who's paying you?
(J Weekly)
Can you just lift his legs?
Sure!
Thanks. Ready? 3...2...1...pull!
What? You tore off his legs!
What are you doing?
Stop filming.
I got it!
Let's check the replay.
Cheers!
This office is huge and awesome.
Jarvis, your backer must be loaded.
Our channel gathered a lot of followers
and people are topping up.
The Boss should be pleased.
You're the brilliant one, Jarvis.
Even bit part actors like us
are now recognized by people on the street.
I can bring glory to the family.
Wait...you're the bit part actor, not me.
Quit bickering...
You're the one...
Your work brought J Weekly to new heights.
Here's your share of the money.
Thanks, Jarvis!
Thanks.
Peter, this is for you.
Auntie Ching...
For me?
Thanks!
It'll take longer to clean a bigger place.
I hope you'll keep expanding.
Thanks.
I'll make sweet soup for you.
Thanks, Auntie Ching.
Folks, this is just the beginning.
We'll be making much more.
Jarvis, how much more? (Hiccup)
I like the sound of that.
Let's aim for the homophone of a hiccup.
A hiccup?
100 million?
100 million!
The jerk is ruthless to toy with
one of ours.
He's the scumbag, remember?
Ngai Ka-yan, you set me up?
What are you talking about?
You claimed to let me run a new channel.
That was just the bait to set me up.
Why would I do that?
Because you're jealous.
You're scared we would surpass you
and replace you.
That's why you're desperate.
Will Jarvis fall for it?
He already put on half of his wetsuit.
It got out of hand.
There's no turning back now.
Miss Tai Yat-sze, we have questions for you.
Before anything happened to Ngai Ka-yan,
you handed him a blue cylinder,
he inhaled from it and passed out.
What else do you know?
Sir, Jarvis asked me to take a gas cylinder
he prepared for himself from his backpack.
Ngai Ka-yan prepared it
for himself beforehand?
No wonder Tsang Chun-kit insisted
he only made 20 cylinders,
but we found 21 at the scene.
Ngan Ka-yan couldn't have prepared
a gas cylinder to kill himself.
I don't know how it happened...
Why did he ask you to take
the cylinder from his backpack?
He said Tom and Paul are traitors.
Those two ingrates planned to trick me
with a stink bomb during the livestreaming.
But I prepared a real oxygen cylinder
for myself.
I'll play dead after I inhale from it
and scare the crap out of them.
That's why I took the cylinder
from his backpack like he said.
I held onto it the whole time,
to make sure I won't mix them up.
Then I handed it to Jarvis
during the livestreaming.
The killer obviously knew beforehand
Ngai Ka-yan prepared a real
oxygen cylinder for himself,
and waited for a chance to swap it
with a high concentration of H2S.
Miss Tai, you need to understand,
only you know what happened to the victim.
I only took the gas cylinder
from his backpack
I don't know anything else.
If you don't believe me,
you can check out my chat with Jarvis.
I bought it but I want to take it back
to the office.
I'll come over after I drop it off.
I'm done. I'm coming.
Thanks.
I remember when he arrived
at the restaurant,
it was around 12:15 p.m.,
and he didn't have the backpack.
Before you head out to the pool.
what else did you do?
We had lunch till 2 o'clock,
then went back to his office.
He put the blue cylinder in his backpack
and we headed out to the pool.
At 11:30 a.m., Ngai Ka-yan went out to
buy the cylinder,
then drop it off at the office.
He had lunch with Tai Yat-sze
at around noon.
Between noon and 2 p.m.,
Ngai Ka-yan left the cylinder in his office.
At 2 p.m. he went back to get it and
pick up his backpack.
Tai Yat-sze said Ngai Ka-yan took the
cylinder from the cabinet,
but that day when we were searching
Ngai Ka-yan's office,
I found another blue cylinder
behind a figurine.
Both blue cylinders were identical.
In the Forensics report,
the victim inhaled from the one
with a high concentration of H2S.
The one found in his office was pure oxygen.
The other 20 were low concentration of H2S.
The killer swapped the high concentration
of H2S with the pure oxygen.
Between noon and 2 p.m.,
is the window for the killer to swap
the two cylinders.
Bring in everyone from the online channel
for questioning.
I checked with the staff,
Peter, the PA and Modem, the I.T. guy
went down to the pool early for set up.
The rest of the staff,
headed out to the pool at 2 p.m.
Miss Lam Sum-ling,
between noon and 2 p.m. on the day
of the incident,
where were you and what were you doing?
I was doing a livestreaming with Paul
from noon to 1:50 p.m.
You were near Ngai Ka-yan's office
during the livestreaming,
between noon and 1:50 p.m.,
you should have seen anyone
in and out of Ngai Ka-yan's office.
Yes, but I don't recall seeing anyone
in and out.
If she was telling the truth,
the only window to do the swap
in Ngai Ka-yan's office
is now down to ten minutes
between 1:50 p.m. and 2 p.m.
Good job just now.
Thanks.
I'll let you wrap up.
I cleaned up the livestreaming room,
and took the garbage to the back stairs.
After that, I went inside the toilet
for a touch up.
After you took out the garbage,
did you go straight to the toilet?
Or did you go somewhere else?
Because I had makeup in my bag,
I went straight to the toilet.
Did you hear any weird noises outside?
No.
Where did you go after you finish
touching up?
I was thirsty, so I went to the pantry
for some water.
Jarvis, Tom and Auntie Ching came in
from the back stairs soon afterwards.
It's almost 2 o'clock.
You should head down to the pool.
All set and ready to go.
Go down for the set up. I'll be down later.
After that, I helped them pack up everything
and headed for the pool.
You said after you finished the
livestreaming with Wendy,
you had a video call,
did you go straight to the conference room?
After I finished the livestreaming,
I went inside the conference room
for the video call.
Right, Mr Cheng...
The video call went rather well,
but while I was talking to the client,
I heard something break outside.
Sorry...that's the gist of the content.
Call me if you need any changes. Bye!
I went outside and saw shards on the floor.
Then Tom came out as well.
Who broke this?
I don't know.
I was in the supplies room checking
the props of the Challenge.
Did you check on the weight belts?
Not yet.
Can you check while I run to the toilet?
Auntie Ching, something is broken,
can you clean this up?
How long were you in the supplies room?
What did you see when you came out?
We didn't have that many weight belts.
It didn't take me too long to check.
When I came out, I saw Jarvis, Tom
and Auntie Ching
come in from the back stairs.
I also saw Wendy come out of the pantry.
Then Tom and I packed up everything
and headed to the pool.
Tsang Chun-kit, on that day,
between 1:50 p.m. to 2:00 p.m.,
what were you doing at the office?
Paul and Wendy had a livestreaming,
I was in the supplies room checking on
the props.
Who broke this?
I don't know.
I was in the supplies room checking
the props of the Challenge.
Did you check on the weight belts?
Not yet.
Can you check while I run to the toilet?
What did you do after you came out
of the toilet?
I came out of the toilet...
Auntie Ching, you haven't cleaned up
the shards?
Let me help you.
Great!
I helped her clean that up
and we threw it out to the back stairs.
Jarvis came back at that time
and the three of us went back
into the office.
Tom, what are you doing here?
You have nothing better to do?
Get back in...
Wendy came from the pantry
and Jarvis told us to head down to the pool.
Paul, Wendy and I left in a hurry.
Yuen Kit-ching, at 1:50 p.m. on that day,
were you in the pantry?
Yes, I was making red bean soup.
After I finished making it,
I went outside and saw shards on the floor.
Tom came from the toilet.
Why are there shards on the floor?
Auntie Ching, you haven't cleaned up
the shards?
Let me help you.
Great!
There should be a noise when something broke
you should have heard it.
My daughter gave me a Bluetooth headphone,
I was trying it out
and didn't hear anything else.
Then what happened?
Tom helped me throw out the shards
in the back stairs.
Jarvis came back at the same time
and the three of us went back
inside the office together.
Then Wendy came out of the pantry.
And Paul came from the supplies room
with some props.
Go down for the set up. I'll be down later.
According to the four of them,
at 1:50 p.m. on that day,
that's what happened at the office.
We're missing someone.
Tai Yat-sze.
After Jarvis and I finished lunch,
he drove me back to his office.
He said he wanted a smoke in the parking lot
and I had a slight bellyache,
so I went up to use the toilet.
Was there anyone else inside?
Not when I went in.
Inside the stall, I heard the door
opened and closed.
Someone must have come in and went out.
Do you remember how long it was
between the door opening and closing?
I'm not sure.
But there was no one there
when I came out of the stall.
Other than the door opening and closing,
did you hear anything else?
No!
Then what happened?
Like I told you before,
Jarvis took a blue cylinder from a drawer
and put it in his backpack.
Then he grabbed the backpack, locked up
and headed for the pool.
Everything they said fits,
with no contradictions.
But timewise, we have blind spots.
Blind spots?
Tai Yat-sze said she heard the door
open and close,
Wendy came in, Wendy went out.
But after Wendy left,
did she go straight to the panty?
Nobody knows.
Wendy could prove Hung Tzi-long
went into the conference room,
and he met Tsang Chun-kit in the hallway,
but how long was Tsang Chun-kit
in the supplies room?
Nobody can vouch for that.
They all had an alibi at some point,
Tsang Chun-kit ran into Hung Tzi-long,
but how long was he in the toilet?
And Yuen Kit-ching...
when we showed up to search for evidence,
there was a pot of sweet soup in the pantry,
but how long was she there?
Nobody could confirm.
And someone was lying.
Someone who made use of
the blind spot in time,
went inside Ngai Ka-yan's office
and swapped the cylinders.
Wendy, can you go with me to see
Cigarette To the day after tomorrow?
I need to discuss something with you.
Jarvis?
(120 minute review of Chief J's
classic pranks)
The first time I saw Jarvis' videos,
was four years ago Christmas.
Jarvis' pranks on a loving couple
along the harbor front
really made my day.
He let off a stink bomb in the subway,
he also livestreamed a prank on the cops.
He came away unscathed even
after he was arrested.
I dare say in the dotcom world,
Jarvis is the most creative and
daring creator.
We narrowed down the window
for the swap to ten minutes.
But we had no idea how to proceed.
All five of them collaborated
on their statements?
That's why they're flawless?
Doesn't look like it.
But someone is lying.
Let's start checking their backgrounds.
Who broke the mug? Fess up!
Not me...watch where you're going.
That's right! Nobody fessed up.
The killer broke the vase?
But we examined the shards
and found no fingerprints or skin tissues.
I still think Tsang Chun-kit and
Hung Tzi-long are the prime suspects.
Because they're in charge of the cylinders.
Someone swapped the cylinder
that killed Ngai Ka-yan.
It would appear they had nothing
to do with it.
Talking about a motive,
Tsang Chun-kit is definitely
the prime suspect.
Is it possible when they were
making the stink bombs,
they made an extra one with
a high concentration of H2S
then swap it again
to kill Ngai Ka-yan?
Let's focus on those two.
Ko Sir!
Cheong...
The Commercial Crime Bureau called me today
and asked about Ngai Ka-yan.
Why the CCB?
They're onto a businessman called Fung To,
who goes by the nickname Cigarette To,
who's suspected of using shell companies
to launder money.
He often placed ads with online channels
or title sponsored their content
with loads of money.
The money is linked to Ngai Ka-yan?
These shell companies had
frequent transactions
with 8 accounts under Ngai Kan-yan's name.
Typical kickback.
Now we have a new lead,
all thanks to the CCB.
They have been tailing Cigarette To
for a long time.
This guy's operation is watertight.
But someone got into a fight in his office
and that's how word got out.
And that someone was Ngai Ka-yan?
Ngai Ka-yan and Tsang Chun-kit
got into a fist fight.
Tsang Chun-kit is getting kickback too?
The power struggle at the channel is fake.
The real motive was over money.
Better question them again.
Hung Tzi-long may know something too.
Why bother? They must be partners in crime.
You're seldom so certain about something.
Because our TCD colleagues decrypted the
computers of the channel staff.
There's more to Hung Tzi-long
than meets the eye.
This is a screen cap of a chat group.
We found this on your computer.
How do you explain that?
Where did this come from?
I never opened this account
or asked these questions.
Seven days ago, you DM'd a
high school Chemistry teacher.
You asked, "Can you make H2S?"
"Do you have details?" "Can you teach me?"
He replied, "Yes, you need simple tools."
"What do you need it for?"
You said it was for teaching.
He asked you, "Are you teaching
students? Be careful."
"Kids don't know any better,"
"there may be accidents"
"because high concentration of H2S
is dangerous and lethal.
Sir, I didn't ask any of that.
I didn't know high concentration of
hydrogen sulfide is lethal.
Did I say hydrogen sulfide?
I know H2S is hydrogen sulfide.
But I didn't know...
This conversation can prove you're lying.
Save your crap for the judge.
No...what must I say before
you'll believe me?
Where did you and Paul learn how
to make a stink bomb?
I bought everything. What about the formula?
Done.
I remember now...
Tom and I were making the stink bombs
in a factory building.
Ask him, he used my computer
to search online.
He can clear me.
No, I didn't use his computer.
Your statement is bad for Hung Tzi-long.
You're sure you didn't remember it wrong?
No.
OK. Now it's your turn.
Did you know beforehand about Ngai Ka-yan
getting kickbacks from Fung To,
a.k.a. Cigarette To?
Why do you ask?
You were irresponsive to our questions
and gave us the run around.
Look at your reaction when
we mentioned kickbacks.
What are you hiding?
Don't try to frame me.
I didn't take any kickbacks.
But your fight with Ngai Ka-yan
in Cigarette To's office
is the talk of the town.
Jerk! How dare you tread on my turf!
I learnt the dirty tricks from you, scumbag!
If I knew you'd be such a mad dog,
I wouldn't have brought you on board.
I should let you die on the streets.
Keep up with your pranks.
You don't need a mad dog like me
to bite you.
You'll do it to yourself eventually.
What are you talking about?
What?
Stop! Don't fight...You just want money.
You want to fight Ngai Ka-yan
for Cigarette To's kickback,
that's why there's a grudge between
you and Ngai Ka-yan.
But Ngai Ka-yan preempted you.
That's why you and Paul made a cylinder
of a high concentration of H2S
and killed him during the livestreaming.
I did not.
Well? Did Tom clear my name?
He insisted he never touched your computer.
Tsang Chun-kit, why did you lie?
You have nothing to say to me?
Why did you drag me in?
Why did you deny using my computer
to learn how to make H2S?
You meant to use me as the scapegoat
from the start?
I treated you like my pal, but you treated
me like a fool.
You did it once and you did it again.
Each time I hit rock bottom,
I have you to thank.
(Two years ago)
Tsang Chun-kit, you swore to me
the goods are in high demand,
that's why I bought them.
But nobody wanted it. I want my money back.
What? Don't be absurd!
Where did you get that watch?
I have known you for years,
you conned me just to buy this?
Get your hands off me.
You scratch it, you pay for it.
Return the goods. I only want my money.
Return? You want to return them
because you can't sell them?
You're out of your mind!
No? Give me the watch. I'll sell it.
Hey...
It's a fake!
I never said it was real.
Are you just as big a sucker as I am?
We're already in debt,
why drink this expensive beer?
You rather be sober and owe $600K?
Or be drunk and owe $600K plus $500?
Take another swig.
If I run into someone like this
at the TV station,
I'd make an about turn.
But when you said you had perks for me,
I truly believed you and bought the stuff.
I won't feel guilty about it.
We've been had because we were greedy
and deserved what we got.
Here...
Wait...you had speaking parts in
several comedies
and the response was good.
Why did you get into pyramid selling?
You know we live from paycheck
to paycheck in this business.
I was looking for a backup plan
but got scammed.
You're quite gifted as an actor.
You shouldn't end up like this.
Yeah...in a few years,
our names will be on online charts of
top ten talented bit part actors.
At least people recognize us.
I don't mind waiting
as long as I can continue to act.
Let's hope the loan sharks
won't kill us first.
Can you be more positive?
We were greedy this time,
if we keep our feet on the ground,
I'm sure we can turn things around.
OK...you'll be my witness.
I, Tsang Chun-kit, do solemnly swear,
I'll never be greedy again
or let anyone else con me again.
That's so corny, but I like it.
I, Hung Tzi-long, do solemnly swear,
I'll never let Tsang Chun-kit con me again.
You should pray that you won't let
other people con you.
Let's both swear, as pals
we'll never let anyone con us again.
OK!
We'll never let anyone con us again.
I never expected working for Jarvis
would make me famous and make money.
We pull pranks on people,
but we never hurt anyone.
We wanted to act and we did it.
I was really having a good time.
Jarvis has changed too.
He became callous and he set us up.
I'm afraid we'll become like him some day.
Luckily, you came forward every time
and stood up to him.
I really thought you were a kindred spirit.
But you only wanted to hurt me.
He didn't clear your name,
because he wanted to steal from Ngai Ka-yan
a business tycoon called Cigarette To.
He wanted the kickbacks for himself.
But Ngai Ka-yan saw through him.
That's why he wanted him dead.
You pretended to get even with Jarvis
by pulling a prank on him.
But you have an ulterior motive.
You wanted to use me to kill him,
then you can get kickbacks for yourself.
We swore we'd be brothers,
but you played me for a fool.
I know it's hard for you to believe me.
But I did not.
Then why didn't you clear my name?
Cat got your tongue?
You're holding out on me,
how do you expect me to believe you?
I'm sorry. But something bad will happen
if I told the truth.
What could be worse than me
being accused of murder?
Relax!
You volunteered to give a statement
only to help your pal?
But I'll be hurting someone I respect.
From a business perspective,
Jarvis is making money for the company
and advertisers trust him.
To put it nicely, I'm in charge of Little J.
But Jarvis actually calls the shots.
Hegemony is not exactly healthy
for the company.
Perhaps...I can be useful to you.
He's holding out on the advertisers.
Most of the money came from Cigarette To.
This guy is a known miser.
Why would he spend so much money
on our channel?
You suspect Jarvis is accepting kickbacks?
I can't go after our bread winner.
Leave that to me. I'll get the evidence.
One day, while Mr. Tsui summoned
Jarvis to a meeting,
I made a copy of his transaction record
and gave it to Mr. Tsui.
Mr. Tsui.
You're no longer at Jarvis' disposal.
I went through the numbers carefully.
Each time Jarvis gets a kickback,
he'd transfer money into your bank account.
I realized the gravity of the matter
and am still deciding what to do.
I like you from the start,
that's why I've been grooming you,
hoping when you're ready,
you can help me keep Jarvis in line.
I'm glad you didn't let me down.
In the end, I gave him the USB.
Jarvis no longer has anything on Mr. Tsui,
that's why he decided to take a chance
and told me to approach Cigarette To
to inform him we don't allow kickbacks.
If you never accepted any kickbacks,
then you don't have a motive
to kill Ngai Ka-yan.
Why did you use Hung Tzi-long's computer
to look up how to make the lethal gas
and frame him for it?
It wasn't me who used the computer.
All set. The high school teacher agreed
to give use the H2S formula.
You really want to increase
the H2S concentration?
I'm worried something bad would happen.
We have different sources that confirmed
a higher concentration will only
make you excited,
sting the eyes and cause nausea.
It's far from being lethal.
Our intention was to trick Jarvis,
I'm afraid...
But a stink bomb has no impact.
Making him teary-eyed and cough
won't convince Cigarette To that
Jarvis' way is passe
and he's no longer the king of pranks.
It won't convince him to deal with us.
But...
Increase the concentration a bit.
Make Jarvis shoot of his mouth
in front of the camera.
It'll be fine. You're a smart guy. Bye.
You followed the formula,
kept Hung Tzi-long in the dark
and increased the H2S concentration.
Between 1:50 p.m. and 2:00 p.m.,
you claimed you were in the supplies room
and you went to the toilet.
That was a lie.
You went inside Ngai Ka-yan's office
to swap the cylinder, right?
No...I was lying.
I wasn't in the supplies room.
I was in the storeroom.
I needed to protect myself.
I printed and kept a copy of
the transaction record.
But since my big fight with Jarvis,
I was worried he might find the hard copy.
So I shredded it in the office.
When I was down to the last few pages,
I heard something broke in the hallway,
I was worried about getting caught.
So I went outside to take a look
and I saw Paul...
Who broke this?
I don't know.
I was in the supplies room checking
the props of the Challenge.
The point is, I didn't listen to Mr. Tsui.
I didn't make a cylinder with
a higher concentration.
I only meant to trick Jarvis,
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
I only made an ordinary stink bomb.
The one Jarvis used was not mine.
Then it must be Mr. Tsui.
He found out you didn't listen to him,
he made one himself.
I don't think he did it.
He didn't show up at the channel that day.
How did he swap it?
Mr. Tsui didn't show up
but he could have an accomplice.
And it was you.
You said you didn't do it,
did you see anyone break the vase?
Or anyone in and out of
Ngai Ka-yan's office?
No. I told you everything I know.
You should know what you just said,
cannot clear you as a murder suspect.
I know. I only told you everything
because I don't want to implicate Paul.
Try to answer all the messages
sent to the channel.
Whatever they said,
we have a duty to respond.
I'll speak to Helen about wrapping up
the livestreaming.
OK!
Hey!
Paul?
They let you out?
Where's Tom?
Still in custody.
He swapped Jarvis' cylinder?
You knew?
Daisy told us.
The Police investigation is still on.
Within those ten minutes, I had an alibi.
Tom admitted the stink bomb was his idea.
The Police let me go because
I'm the least likely suspect.
Why was Mr. Tsui brought in
for questioning?
The Police suspect Mr. Tsui had
a disagreement with Jarvis
that prompted him to resort to murder.
But they didn't have enough to charge him
because he was in a client meeting
the whole day
and was not at the scene.
They could only charge him for
conspiring to murder.
Tom is still the prime suspect.
Did Tom do it?
I have no proof.
But I have known him long enough,
he's nothing like that.
Looks can be deceiving.
I'm glad you're back.
You can help run Little J Media.
But Auntie Ching quit.
Why?
She's been having nightmares
since Jarvis died.
She'll be here till month end.
Who'd want to stay and be reminded of him?
You want to leave too?
You never agreed with Jarvis' style.
Go ahead, let the channel fall apart.
Let Jarvis' effort go to waste.
(Three months after the incident)
I didn't expect there's a case within
Ngai Ka-yan's case.
Too bad we don't have enough to
charge Mr. Tsui.
I've been digging these past three months,
but we have no solid proof.
Tom and Mr. Tsui are
particularly suspicious.
Within those ten minutes before
Ngai Ka-yan left with the lethal gas,
no one could verify the exact position
of the other five people.
I still think Tsang Chun-kit
is the prime suspect.
Was he being unusually honest
and volunteered everything about Mr. Tsui?
Or he did it to cover up a bigger lie?
This is too brain burning.
I can't take this anymore.
These kids may have the answer for us.
Yo, it's Agent J again.
We have a new game for you.
It's called Pick Your Pigswill.
Here, we have two buckets,
one is water, the other is pigswill.
If you pick the bucket with the water,
you'll get $20K and other prizes.
Without further ado, let's begin...
They're both pigswill!
What are you doing?
Split!
Run...
Are you OK?
This pin is the same as the one
found in Ngai Ka-yan's office.
Is it connected to his death?
Why do they have this pin?